Let's [music]
dance.
Let's dance. I need you. You [music]
need me to settle. All that I see. I
recolor
[singing]
switch lanes [music] when the fame don't
come. Now I'm praying that the pain
stay.
Do [music]
I'm shimmering
[music]
winner
baby pull up in my
promising
no
[music]
I said if I do just baby
I'm you [music] let go. No, I said
people say we let go. I said you just
[music]
people.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. [music]
Uh-huh.
Ah.
I got the love on me. Ah. [music]
I got [music]
my no
[music]
love
when I let [music]
I said if I do justice baby
you let [music]
I say people say we let [music]
just peopleh
[music]
[music] I got the love on meh Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
Ah. [music]
I got to love
you. Thank you. Thank you.
[music]
>> [music]
>> We the children of [music] light and we
will never let up. Never giving up
fighting. [music]
We didn't make it through the night.
Yeah. Done the crawling all night but
keep your [singing] head up. We were
made for this life. Yeah. [music]
Wait to see how we rise up. We been down
for too long. Waiting for a come up.
Better [music] days around the corner.
All the pain are stronger. Yeah, we
aiming for the long run. Keep [music] on
surviving in this war for no reason. Now
we changing the season.
Storm is [music] over now. Storm is over
now. Storm is over. [music]
Guys, we have arrived, but we've not
gone to our room yet. We're just quickly
grabbing lunch because the restaurant
closes at
>> 4 and we have 10 minutes. So, we're
going to eat and then go check out our
room and then I'll show you guys the
resort. This is one of the restaurants
and then I'll explain everything to you
guys. Yeah. Right.
>> The storm is over [music] now. Storm is
over now.
is over. Promise by [music]
a I
[music]
change is coming tonight. I can see the
sky start to clear up. [music] We've
been waiting for life. Oh, never giving
up the fight.
Start a countdown right now. About to
take off. Yeah, it's [music] our time to
rise up
like we been down for too long. Wait for
a come up days around the corner. All
the pain [music]
stronger. Yeah, we in for the long run.
Keep on surviving in this war for no
reason. [singing and music] Now we
changing the season. Yeah, the storm is
over now. [music] The storm is over now.
I say storm is over now.
Storm is over [music] now. Storm is over
now. I say storm is over now. [music]
[music]
Hey
I [music]
[music]
Hey guys, we've just landed in the Mald.
It's time for the room tour. So, I'm
going to show you that we actually have
beach access. So, I'm going to start
with that and show you. So, we come down
there. There's actually beach access
right here that we have. And you can see
those other villas
over there. And you can see people's
rooms, but our room is the last room
here. So, we don't look at anyone else's
room. So, this is the beach. Then you
walk up there. Okay.
And it's so nice. So, this is actually
considered winter, I think, on this side
or low season. So, it's actually
affordable to book it now. But it's very
it's still hot. As a South African, this
is extremely hot for me.
Right.
Hello, MTV.
Welcome to my crib. Why Why is it
scanning? Okay, so we start the side,
guys. We have I'm not sure if this is a
king-size
bed,
probably a king-size bed. And then we've
got the
lamp shades on both sides. We have a
seating area over here. We have another
seating area over here. I think this is
an all-inclusive resort, but we did do
the all-inclusive package. So, we have
these drinks over here that are
included. These are restocked every
single day. So if you're going to have
gin and whatever, like tomorrow when
they clean the room, they'll refill
this. So you get three of these a day.
And that's what we have. And then they
just showed us cups and stuff stay in
these drawers.
Got glasses,
snacks. These are also included. Get re
um filled once a day. Then in here we've
got our mini bar which also has one Oh,
Dr. Hoff. That's from No, I think so.
So, this also gets refilled once a day
if you have any of these things like
refilled once a day. So, yeah, this is
the room. Our bags. Then we have our
closet here. We also have our slippers
that we are allowed to use and I think
we're allowed to take
gowns. They also give you a steamer.
They showed me a steamer. Yeah, the
handheld steamer that is in here. And
then I'm going to show you the outside,
guys. Let me just bring the ISO down.
Then this is the outside because we have
our bathtub here. It's quite humid a
bit. And then this is like the get ready
with me station. We've got our towels
over here
and sink. You brush your teeth. You can
hear the ocean. There's a little mirror
for me to get ready. And I think I can
use that stool to sit. There is just
like this wide mirror. Then you have
your indoor shower. I think this is like
just in case it's raining. We have the
indoor shower. But we also have an
outdoor shower like if you just want to
like shower outside which is really big
guys. It's extremely extremely big.
Yeah, this is it. And then let me go
show you guys the outside
from here. We walk to the outside.
Oh, I almost walked into this.
The outside we have another seating area
over here. Um,
over there we have a life jackets in
here. These are our neighbors. And then
on this side, we don't have any
neighbors. We have a deck for sleeping.
And then we have our pool over here,
the pool.
Then we have the net. Obviously, Maldes,
it's never the same without a net. And
then this leads you down into the ocean
to swim. They just said we should not go
further beyond that reef. So, we can
swim all the way, but not further than
that. And from here, you can actually
see Mali because this is actually 7
minutes away from the airport.
I can see a plane landing. Um, I just
wanted to show you guys there's actually
a family in the water somewhere there
diving.
Yeah, there's a family diving. Yeah,
guys, this is it.
B copyright.
Every now and then you got to remember
you're a YouTuber. So,
let's get dressed. I just took a shower,
washed my hair after I did the,
you know, the trending video that people
do when they arrive in the mouths where
you show the room tour and you jump into
the pool and into the ocean. I had just
arrived. Jumped into my uh the ocean
with my clothes and then so obviously my
hair needed to be washed because we're
going to our first dinner.
And
yeah, it needs to dry properly and I
needed to detangle it because when it
went in there, it just tangled a bit.
Not like tangling tangling. This is how
much hair I usually lose like after a
wash. And this is normal because tracks
like obviously are not strong enough to
hold your hair. You shouldn't be losing
any more than this amount of hair. So,
every time I wash, this is pretty much
how much I lose. And that's why they
always say with time, like I think after
like a year or two, you will add an
additional bundle to your hair. You
don't need to change the hair. You just
add like an additional bundle.
So, I want to do my face quickly.
Let me get my makeup. I think I want to
put like
Thank goodness I packed a lash because I
kind of felt like because of all this
water I'm going to be losing lashes
quickly. So I am probably going to add a
stick on lash on top of this just to
give it a little bit of a pizzazz.
So let's get my makeup back. Guys, I
don't know if you can see it, but the
makeup currently doesn't want to stick
to my face. It's humid.
I don't know what to do.
We are going to try and get a face, but
if this doesn't work. Oh my goodness.
What do you mean I can't do my face?
But I tried giving it time to dry, but
like it's just sitting there looking
muddy like a puddle, which is like
confusing me.
E, I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to And it's not
helping that I'm actually doing my
makeup outside. I did try and put on the
fan to see if that will help, but this
whole get ready station is situated out.
Like look, I just look like
really
money, guys.
Let me try and blend it out with a brush
and see if that works.
Makeup brush.
Something is working.
Yo, and this is like so warm. Like it's
almost hot. Came out of the hot bar. I
think I got a makeup look. I think this
will work for night one. Um, I just need
to do I don't know if that recorded, but
I was saying I feel like this will work
for night one. Um,
this came out really hot. It's drying. I
want to just do my bottom mascara and
then I think we are good. I just need to
figure out I just need to put like
lotion. Get the body to glisten. And do
I want a little bit of highlight? I
think I could use the eye shadow I just
used now as a bit of highlighter.
I do it here. I'm just going to use this
as a bit of highlighter.
Hi guys. Okay, so we're off to dinner.
Um, I'm actually just going to put in
the outfit video here so you guys can
see. I'm going to try get some photos. I
don't I think after dinner because now
we are rushing to dinner. So, this is
how I look for day one in the Maldes
after running up and down the pool. We
look really cute. Yeah. So, I'll see
y'all.
[music]
>> [music]
>> church.
[music]
Let's go. Let's dance. Let's dance. I
need [music] you. You need me [singing]
to settle. All that I see. I recolors
[music]
[music] when the rain pour. Switch lanes
when the fame don't come. Now I'm
praying that the pain stay gone. [music]
But I still feel it when the day has
been long. She want passion without the
scars. Want loyalty but keep on her
guard. How [singing] you testing a bad
man's [music] heart when you still
healing from your last war? I ain't
trying to be too toxic. All the signals
[music] are exhausting. You need space,
but you still
calling. Let's dance, mama. Let's dance.
Let's dance. Let's dance, mama. Let's
dance. Let's dance, mama. Let's dance.
Let's dance. Let's dance.
Let's dance. Let's dance, mama. Let's
dance. Let's dance, mama. Let's dance.
Cold war, but my heart still warm. How
to learn peace in the middle [music] of
storms. They were sleeping on me now to
move along. My mind like l smile. I need
you. You need me. [music]
All that I see. I recap
from I ain't trying to be too [music]
toxic. All the signals are exhausted.
You need space but you're still stuck.
Yeah. Was [music] gone. Why you still
calling?
[music]
>> I was 10 toes when the rain falls
when the fame don't come. Now I'm
[music] praying that the pain stay gone.
How you man's heart.
>> Good morning, guys.
We are at breakfast.
We're so tired. We actually got woken up
by accident.
Room service. Not room service. Was it
is it room service?
>> No, the cleaning service was like
knocking on a door to [music] clean. And
then we're like, "Oh my god, we're late
for breakfast." So, I just quickly
washed my face, brushed my teeth, uh put
on a cute little outfit for breakfast
and made breakfast. And then we are
going to figure out what our plans for
the day are. Probably going to do
snorkeling today. So, I want to get out
so we can get cuz the sun is nice and
Yeah.
So, the water should be warm. Nice and
warm.
But the problem is that the fish are
won't be around. I was about to say the
fish won't be here.
>> In the afternoon. Yeah, cuz if it's too
warm, don't they like go deeper?
>> They do.
In the morning when it's too hot, they
go deeper.
[music]
>> I ain't trying to be too
in this face, but you're still
calling.
Yeah. [music]
[music]
[music] Oh no.
Good morning. Um, we have just come back
from breakfast. We picked up our snorkel
gear because we're going to snorkel
later.
Let me see what we got.
So, this is the snorkel gear we got. Let
me just zoom out. I just realized I'm so
zoomed in. This is the snorkel gear that
you get.
You can pick it up at the diving center
and then you can keep it with you in
your room till like you check out.
Basically
that's included with your stay. So I
know when we looked at the map I think
in our area when we dive here I think it
should be turtles and then the other
side the rooms that their dive area I
think you get to see manta rays. I love
swimming with manta rays in Bali, so I
wouldn't mind spotting a few here. And
I'm sure there's quite a bit of like
fish and stuff. Another thing that I
would really like to do that's an option
is swimming with the nurse sharks. But
like I've just been having this fear
because just after we confirmed our
booking, do you know how like how you
get your algorithm just like feeds you
information based on what you're about
to do? It fed me a video of some girl
who got bit by nurse shark because the
nurse shark thought when she was like
moving her hand she was trying to feed
it and it actually bit her where the
skin here peeled off like skin here peel
off like you know and she was here for a
while so I'm just like I don't know so
we considering it we might do it
tomorrow we're not going to do it today
we're really tired today like I said we
almost missed breakfast. We got woken up
by the cleaning people. If they didn't
actually just like ring the doorbell, we
would not happen at breakfast on time.
And they really do shut it down at
10:00. And the next time lunchtime is
from
well, we would have just had to wait a
few hours because lunchtime from the
first restaurant is 12:00. All the
restaurants that do lunch, it's from
12:00. So, we can do lunch, but we're
pretty full. I don't know if we're going
to do lunch.
>> I'm vlogging, babe.
>> I don't see you yet. I think my hair is
covering you, but you can stay right
there. So, anyway, yeah. So, lunch is
until
3:00 and then we would have to then wait
again for dinner. And dinner most places
start either between 6:30 and 7:00 p.m.
So, that's the plan. So, right now, I
think we're just going to finish off
napping because we're both tired because
the sun is still pretty high. It's maybe
too hot to snorkel right now and then
we're going to snorkel later. The sun is
also still too hot to even go into our
pool right here. The sun is right on top
of the pool, so I'm not planning to do
that. Probably going to have a drink and
then go back to sleep. I'm just going to
try guava juice. I don't understand why
this guava juice is this color. I would
normally expect guava juice to be pink,
but their guava seems to look like
really yellow even on the image. I had
the juice yesterday.
Um,
I had the normal cocktail juice and that
tasted more like guava than Well, this
tastes like guava. It's just the color.
Breakfast was nice. The food here is so
nice. It's not bad. It's not It's very
It's very healthy. So, you can taste
that everything is made with like with
health in mind. So, I'm like really not
stressed about putting on a bit of
weight this week, but we're not eating
that much as well. Like,
yeah, we're just eating really good
portions. It's like I don't know what it
is about your mind. The minute you know
everything is included, you just don't
want to eat that much cuz it's an
all-inclusive resort. So like everything
there is there for you to eat. So now
you become I feel like you become
overwhelmed. Even now I was excited
about the mini bar, but like I haven't
touched any of the alcohol. But if I was
paying for it, I would want it. I don't
know why the brain does that to you. No,
no, [music] no. Loving you would be like
one minute of fire, one minute of rain,
one minute [music] of pleasure, one
minute with stressing, one minute of
pain.
We keep on quiet but heavy on [music]
the L. One minute of passion, then you
want attention. No, I guess I would
have. [music]
They feel that one voice. They hear that
one voice. They feel that one choice.
[music]
Now we find inside. Oh, they had that
one voice. They had that one choice.
[music]
Now you be my choice.
Guys, we're about to go snorkeling now.
Just got back from lunch. What I'm
deciding is whether I'm snorkeling with
a life jacket or not, cuz it's pretty
far out where we have to go. It's not
that far out, but let me just show you
where we're going. Um, and I'm not sure
cuz like I said drinking. I'm not sure
if I'm gonna get tired halfway. And I'll
need like that life jacket just to help
me like stay. So, I might put it on and
then
um
and then take it off further out if I
want to dive in cuz I want to do dive. I
want to dive in and see like the fishies
and the life jacket is going to keep me
afloat. So, we'll see. So, we're going
around this reef area. Yeah, that's how
far we have to swim out. Um, the dark
parts are probably where we're going to
see a lot more stuff than the lighter
parts. I can see around here there's no
fish or anything like that. So,
yeah, I'm going to take you guys with me
on the DG.
[music]
One minute I fire, one minute you fire.
Leave me with the pain. One [music]
minute attention. Girl, don't even
mention no gas. And I would have sight.
Oh, they feel that one voice. [music]
They had that one voice. They feel that
one choice. Now weight. Oh, they had our
one voice. [music]
They had that one choice. Now you be my
choice. Heat. Heat. Heat.
[music]
I have one.
[music] Maybe I guess I would have
inside. Oh, they feel that one voice.
[music] They had that one voice. They
feel that one choice. Now we inside. Oh,
they had that one voice. [music]
They had that one choice. Now you be my
choice.
One voice. One voice.
One choice.
One voice.
Now you be mine. You be mine.
What is that?
I thought I s
Okay.
>> [music]
>> What you never do?
I [music]
wish you got mine.
>> [music]
>> We want to chill.
[music]
This jackpot.
It's not too [music] late.
It's not too late for us. It's not too
late.
Oh, [music]
it's not too late.
It's not too late for [music] us. It's
not too late.
And all you got to do is hold on.
[music] Hold on.
Hold on.
And all you got to do is [music] hold
on.
Hold on.
Hold on. [music]
And all you got to do is
if I only see this [music]
jackpa
this [music]
Oh baby
[music]
it is what it is. It's not too late.
It's not too late for us. It's not too
late. [music]
It's not too late.
>> Yeah, guys. We're just floating in the
ocean.
Yes. Just floating here.
The water is nice. It's warm.
I remember somewhere over there.
Yeah.
Welcome to the good life.
>> Welcome to the good life.
>> Yeah.
>> Where?
Oh,
what the hell am I floating over there?
Guys, I spot out a stingray. My camera
isn't on. Okay,
>> I'm trying to swim and find it. I think
it went the other way.
Guys, I'll see you later to show off. I
just swam out of the beach here. I'm
tired because the distance between my
room and the beach, the beach was
closer. So, and thank goodness the room
is right next to the beach. So, I'm
going to walk this way. My boyfriend's
still on the water. He says he will come
in to the room.
What the hell is that?
Oh, no ways.
He locked me out.
Guys, I can see my boyfriend is having a
nice shower.
He's having a nice shower. I'm stuck out
here and I keep knocking and trying to
open the door
and he locked the door.
Why' you lock the door?
>> Why would they come in?
>> Well, you lock me out
>> and you're having a nice shower and I'm
watching you shower here.
>> You're like there.
>> Why are you peeking through the big
>> Do you know I even went back there to
walk to see if you're still swimming cuz
I've been sitting here on the floor.
>> Oh, sorry. You [music]
>> all
[music]
hold on.
And [music] all you got to do is hold
[singing] on.
Hold on.
[music] Hold on.
And all you got to do is hold on.
>> [music]
>> I'm supposed to be doing
outfit of the day over here, but you can
tell there's maintenance because the air
con is leaking.
Leing onto everything. So, we're just
going to do outfit when I come back.
Outfit of the day, guys. So, I am
wearing this two-piece. It does like
like has a little peepphole moment
situation here with the shorts. This is
a two-piece from Sheen. I think the
brand is KZ N or something. And I really
like how my hair dried out today. It
looks so gorge. I don't know where I'm
going to place you guys. Let me place
you guys somewhere so I can show you my
outfit properly.
So, this is it. Shorts, [snorts]
top. It's so hot and humid. I need lots
of water. I need a drink. It's a real
drinky drink. Look cute.
Yeah, I like it. Guys, what do you
think? And then I just wore these Steve
Madden sandals. That's what I'm wearing.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Good morning, guys. Yo, so last night we
spent the whole day at the bar. Well,
well, the whole evening at the bar. Then
we overslept.
Then we forgot. We put one alarm. We put
one alarm because I wanted us to watch
the sunrise cuz it's actually a pretty
pretty sunrise and I wanted to capture
it for you guys. So, we put that alarm
on. Then when it came, my camera has
started this thing where you record, you
record for 10 seconds and it switches
off and it grates me every time it does
this. So, I'm just going to keep talking
in bits
and then I'll just edit. So, this
morning we ended up like saying, "Okay,
let's not watch the sun rise. We're too
tired. Let's go to sleep." We did go to
sleep at 2:00 in the morning. So, we're
like, "We'll
do this again. We'll try this again
tomorrow." We forgot we didn't put an
alarm for breakfast. Housekeeping wakes
us up at 4 minutes to 10:00, guys. There
was no way we're going to make it to
breakfast because we are so far from
where the breakfast happens. You need to
wait for a buggy which takes between 5
to 10 minutes to get here and then it's
going to take another 5 to 10 minutes to
get you wherever you're going. So, we
missed breakfast but thank goodness this
is all inclusive. So, lunch at all the
restaurants starts from 12:00 again. So,
we just showered. He's showering. I just
got out the shower. We're gonna go have
lunch and then we still have room. Like
if we're not full at lunchtime, they
still have this hour for they call it
high tea between 4:00 and 5. So we still
have time to eat again then in case like
we decide we want to snorkel and do
things because there there's a break
after that between dinner. Dinner only
then starts again at like 6:30.
And the only snacks they put in this
room is like peanuts. So yeah, we're
going to have lunch and then we're
probably going to do high tea. Yo, it is
so hot. And you know, thank goodness
we didn't follow the weather report cuz
the weather report had said it would
rain. Now that we're here, it's actually
not going to rain. It is not going to
rain. It is raining the day after we
leave, which is nice. So yeah, let me
just get dressed for breakfast. I just
took my hair out of the bonnet um from
last night. This is how it looks. I'm
going to spray it with a bit of water.
So, it looks a bit put together. I
didn't [clears throat] put much product.
This is from me swimming in the ocean. I
just rinsed my hair um after Oh, there's
a plane going.
There's a plane going. Like, it's a big
plane. So, it's obviously going to
whatever country that is. I can't see
the the tip, so I don't know what
hairline that is.
That's going to be us soon. So, yeah, I
was saying I didn't put any product in
my hair. So, this is why my I've got a
lot of flyaways. I don't see myself
putting product now. I just want to get
to lunch, but I'm going to make it look
appropriate. I cannot just rock up to
lunch looking like a mess. But, I am on
a
on vacation.
I'm allowed to.
I'm allowed to. So, yeah. Guys,
[sighs and gasps] what a morning,
guys. Did I tell you how hot it is? It
is so hot. Like, you don't even want to
be outside right now. And I'm just like,
I can't believe this is the lower. This
is them. They obviously don't have
winter here,
but their monsoon season is supposed to
be more of like the lower temperature
side of things, but we are in the
equator, so that kind of makes sense. We
are literally on the equator line, so
that's why it probably doesn't get cold.
Um, but yeah, every day that we're here,
it's been between 27 and
29 all day. So, it does not drop lower
than 27. Like even at night, even early
in the morning, it's just consistently
hot. I woke up to go to the bathroom
last night. When I walked out of there,
remember our bathroom is like outside. I
was like, "What in the hell? Why is it
this hot? It's like 3:00 4:00 in the
morning." And I'm like, "This is hot."
So, yeah, it gets really hot, guys. Um,
okay. Yes. Get rest. No, you can't find
a spot right in front of me.
No.
I said not to come on here and brag, but
I think every single one of you deserves
someone that just listens. Okay, so I
remember the last time we went to Bali,
I packed this with me. I actually should
have used my I'll probably use my shower
gel for for dinner. Yeah. Um I remember
saying, "Oh, I really love this new Soul
de Janeiro collection. Like I think this
is my fave." Because I had started off
with the yellow one and then when I got
this as a press pack, I was like, "This
is like my absolute f." And I completely
forgot to get a new one for our trip.
And he ordered me a travel size. But
because he wanted me to pick, he ordered
both this one and the yellow one. So I
was even asking him, I'm like, "How did
you even know where to find this?" And
then he's like, he he just saw like a Do
you see a me a message a popup?
What was it? Yeah. One of the apps,
either Superless or Take a Lot, he just
saw that popup. I think it's because he
spends too much time with me. So all the
stuff that I like pops up on his like
take a lot and superb list. So then when
he saw it, he just added it to the cot.
Checked it out before our vacation and
then when I walked into his place, it
was supposed to be a surprise. He forgot
to hide it. I found it. I found both of
these on the counter. So these are
really cute. And this is what I sprayed
today.
It's extremely hot. I don't know what it
is about the heat here, but when you
step outside,
whatever perfume you're wearing is
immediately like fading. Even if like
your perfume has a longevity
thing. This is perfume body and hair.
Okay, we'll find out. I'm not putting
any heat on this, so it's not going to
burn, but I just want to smell nice. So,
now we're going to lunch, guys. Man, I'M
TAKING YOU WITH ME.
YOU'RE COMING TO LUNCH. You're coming to
lunch. You're coming to lunch. I'm
taking drinks orders right now. Put your
drinks orders in the comment section.
What are you having to drink? I finally
found a good drink after trying so many.
So, I tried a um what did I try before?
I tried a margarita. The margaritas
aren't that great. I think they're
really not that great when it comes to
making cocktails here. Tried margarita.
tried a peach peach spritzer frizz
something something. Then I tried like I
tried four different cocktails. Then I
was like to them cuz I hadn't seen it in
the menu and I think it's because of the
wording that's why they don't put in the
menu. I was like to them do you guys
have a pawn star martini? They're like
yeah we can make you that. Just if you
guys didn't know the Maldives is a
Muslim
country. So, I think that's why they
wouldn't put that specific word in the
menu, but they do have it. So, I was
like, I will have a ponto martini,
please. Had it last night and
takes the cup. So, that's what I'm
ordering. So, let me know. Put it in the
comment section. What is your drinks
order? Okay, [laughter] babe. Okay,
guys. I want to show you my outfit, but
there's something else I wanted to say.
I wanted to just tell you, Hold on. Let
me just get the lighting right.
I was here to tell you that you guys
should date nerds, okay? These people
just want to know info about everything.
The amount of stuff I've learned on this
trip because somebody's always like,
"Hey, Siri." Like, he just asked the
Siri, right? And now he's like, "Hey
Siri, why is some of the parts green and
some of the parts of the ocean in the
Mald blue?" And then Siri's like, "Oh,
whatever whatever reflects."
I learned that. I don't even know what
the real Oh, this lighting doesn't look
that great. Let me move you.
So, oh, okay. This looks so much better.
I just closed the lace here. So, this is
my outfit for the day. And another thing
I learned from from the nerd in this
room today is why the weather is so
consistent. He asked, "Do you ask Siri
or did you just Google it this time?"
>> I had a feeling.
>> You had a feeling and you double checked
it.
>> To Singapore as well.
>> Okay. So because he's been to Singapore,
he had a feeling why the weather is so
consistent. So because it's been between
27 and 20
>> 29, but it feels like 35. I won't lie.
It says 27 to 29 feels like 35. Um, and
that's because we're sitting right on
the equator. And another fact that he
taught me No, did I did I teach you
that?
>> The two seasons. No, not the two
seasons.
No, I I I told you about that one that
um Mali is the lowest country
>> in [clears throat] the world.
>> The 1.5 m to sea level.
>> Yes. So, it's the lowest country in the
world. So, is it in the world?
>> Yeah, it's the lowest country in the
world. And that's why most of the
islands like are very like close to the
bottom of the sea. And that's but that
is the fence. [laughter]
So and they change throughout the day.
No well not even throughout the day
throughout the months the island the
shape of the island changes because of
the way the sand moves and everything.
So between me and him, we are teaching
each other a lot of facts about the
Maldes. But a cute fact we just learned
is that this is the lowest country in
the world. But guys, this is absolutely
beautiful. I feel like everybody needs
to come here. I feel like Asia takes the
cup. Asia takes the cup for out of all
the places we've been traveled, both me
and you combined, which continent do you
pick?
or beach holiday.
>> No, just holiday in general. Not
deciding whether it's beach.
>> Yeah, Asia.
>> Yeah,
>> lots of options.
>> Asia has lots of options for me cuz I
like Europe, but like the churches, the
walking I feel like geometry is Europe.
>> So, yeah.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Still there. [music]
Nobody care. So I talk less. I still
there
one man once more. Yeah, I [music] know.
Yeah, I don't lose and I don't
>> Another night, another dinner.
You don't realize how many times you got
to do your makeup, especially like if
you're trying to create content and like
shoot photos. It's like bus, another
bus, bus, bus, bus, bus, bus, another
bus. So, makeup done already. I've
showered. Going to pick what outfit I'm
wearing tonight.
We're actually having a late dinner
tonight. So, that's that. Our dinner is
at 9:30 because you actually have to
make reservations to some of the
restaurants and the restaurant we wanted
to go to only had a reservation
available at 9:30. So, we're going at
9:30. Um, so yeah, this is the vase.
It's pretty like plain. I was I wasn't
trying to do too much today because I've
been doing my makeup for two days in a
row and I'm like so exhausted of doing
makeup
and I'm going to say it again. I'm
sitting [clears throat] outside and I'm
burning up and you be like, "Why do you
keep doing your makeup outside?" Because
this is the spot for doing makeup. And
I've already set it up so I just don't
want to I'm just committing. I'm just
going to put the fan a little bit higher
though. Um, waiting for babe to go
shower so that he can help me shoot my
content because he has to hold the
lights for me to do my get ready with
me. I didn't do one yesterday because
they were fixing, but I want to try to
do one today. So,
um, hopefully we get we get one and
we'll get few photos before we go for
dinner tonight. So, and I need to figure
out what I'm doing with my hair today.
Um, yeah. Let's see how it looks.
This is what we are wearing to dinner.
It's this two-piece from Emprea.
This is how it look.
And the hair,
I didn't wash it. I slept with it this
afternoon. And this is why I absolutely
absolutely 100% recommend raw hair
because guys, there's so much
versatility.
Well, not like a lot of versatility,
just have curly hair. But like I feel
like you know how it's a struggle to
like wear
wigs on a vacation like this where it's
hot. I 100% recommend pursuing and you
still get that look, cute look you are
going for. For some people will be like,
"Oh, I don't have much hair." If you
don't have a lot of hair, I would
recommend getting a 2x6 closure like I
used to do before my hairline came back.
Like before my hair hairline came back,
I was a 2x6
closure curly.
There are some hair textures that I
still prefer like 2x6. Like if I'm away
straight hair, then we're definitely
going for a 2x6. Especially if I don't
want to keep frying my um leave out
because in terms of my hair, I washed
it, but I haven't straightened it. I
didn't even blow dry it, blow dry it
yesterday after the snorkeling. I just
let it air dry and that's about it. Oh
my gosh, guys. It is so
hot. It is unbearably hot. I just don't
even know what to do. I honestly don't
know what to do anymore. So,
I'm tea, but it's really hot. Guys, I'm
trying to do the outfit of the day, but
the light is dead. And we both thought
we put on charge last night, and it
actually wasn't charging. I don't know
why. So, [snorts] we're going to give it
5 minutes so I can do the outfit of the
day before we go out for dinner. Thank
goodness dinner was 4 9:30
otherwise.
Y that is such a bright spotlight.
Actually we should be using that for the
flash
so you know where to you know we're
advancing your photography levels. So,
>> lighting.
>> H
>> the lighting has
>> Yeah, we need to like
>> advance you a little bit. So, the light.
Yeah. Hey beauties. So, let's say let's
all say thank you to Mr. TG gang for
holding up the light for us.
>> Upgraded. [laughter]
>> So, [snorts] guys, um update. This is
what I'm wearing. I don't know if I
showed it to you, but now we're in
better lighting. So this is my two-piece
from Impreka fragrance. We're still
wearing this one. This is what I wore on
day one. So wearing the same one. And
then we're carrying this bag from Sheen.
Just compliments the outfit with the
brown. And then this bangle is from
Sheen. And then I'm just wearing like
like I think you guys know these
sandals, my Zara sandals. I love wearing
these on vacation. Um like I said,
dinner's at 9. This hair. Just keep an
eye out and you'll find out soon where
to get the hair, okay? I'll keep you on
the loop, you guys. I think you guys
will be the first to know. Um because
you guys are my faves, so you'll be the
first to know. Okay. All right. So,
let's go out for dinner cuz it's so hot.
I am sweating out here. Okay. Let's go.
[music]
The power
I know [music]
I know why you want make all good
everything all right
[music]
and God got me [music] it's all good all
good no matter what you My
student [music]
[music]
all night pray for me every night. Even
[music] when I know they all right
another day,
another breakfast which is called the
bikey should be here.
When the person passing through, we know
never say [music] going to be all right.
I know perfect
but my heart just let me do better now
[music]
ask question I don't get up now you get
the power whenever [music] the hard
me [music]
everything all right [music]
>> [music]
>> Guys, we are off to dinner.
This is what I'm wearing. Outfit of the
day. These earrings.
I think these are from Sailor. The
necklace.
H same jewelry. Not me mentioning her
actual name. Same jewelry by Sailor. I
think both. Um this dress is from Sheen.
It gets tied to the side. It's really
cute. It just looks like got a wrap
around with um body suit situation. Let
me twist you guys so you can see a
little bit more of my
little space here.
There we go. And then I'm just wearing
the white Steve Madden sandals. Funny
thing, my feet are so swollen from the
heat. So, none of my shoes fit right
now. My feet actually look like
you don't want to bring a woman has
swollen feet. That's how my feet look.
It is so bad. But yeah, I'm just going
to take them off when we get to the
restaurant. I just want to show you guys
how I look. It's really hot. We took
photos just now outside and I was
sweating. I even just have to like pop
up on fragrance because funny thing I
thought it was just my perfumes but even
my boyfriend's perfumes are not lasting.
You step outside and whatever you put on
gone. And I thought people here are not
wearing fragrance. No,
the heat here just
doesn't work well with perfume. I don't
know what fragrance works for this area.
Like somebody needs to sell perfume for
high humidity. I like how my hair looks.
It's still wet because I nearly drowned.
I will tell you guys the story
when I come back for dinner on how I
nearly drowned and my boyfriend had to
come out into the ocean and save me. And
I nearly drowned him while he was trying
to save me,
trying to save my ass. And I drowned. So
now he's lying to me and we're always
laughing at the people on my DMs. He's
like, "Now you should ask them would
they save you in a situation where
you're drowning and let's see what what
they say." He's like, "I literally just
saved your life." I'm like, "You
actually did." So cute. I really like
how cute this dress is. Just this whole
outfit is cute. Looks really nice. Yeah.
Let's go. God. [music]
It's all good. It's all good. No matter
what to come my way. Still there.
Still there.
[music] Still there.
[music]
Stud
>> guys with the way the barman here are, I
just decided I'm also capable of being a
barman because that's how the drinks
are. So I have made a mixture of
this. I'm going to say what because
somebody's asking me why I'm not
drinking [laughter]
this drink and that
and that.
And I called it the Maldives
Sunrise. Okay, let's do a taste test.
That's not bad.
It just needs ice. Like it just needs It
wasn't in the fridge that long cuz they
just refilled these now. But it's
honestly
not that bad.
So I don't know what it is about this
juice, but it actually doesn't mix with
the alcohol. The alcohol is floating
here at the top. That's why I keep
saying it's strong.
>> [music]
>> And I want
and I
[music]
call me [singing]
>> [music]
[music]
>> I don't know what you wait for.
Tell me you're tired of the last.
>> Trust me, baby. [music] I'm the man.
Cuz we go dance for this moonlight.
For this [music] moonlight,
for this moon
and we go dance for this [music]
moon right
[music]
[singing]
there. [music]
Need to play [singing]
resisting my
you. [music]
It's nobody business. Me and you a fair.
I don't know when [music] you playing
telling me you're tired of the last
day
>> of doing my makeup.
Um
cuz like I just realized you know what
they say about the Maldives they say
like after a few days after 2 days you
already know the resort. You've like I
think after 3 days you've been to all
the restaurants
you've swam. You've done everything
there is to do.
So now you're just like
what else am I going to do? I've swam
snorkeled. Uh,
I almost drowned. Oh, I didn't tell you
guys how I almost drowned. [laughter]
So, I went in the water and I didn't
realize how strong the current was going
cuz it was like really pushing people
out, was pulling people out. And then I
was snorkeling and I went in there
without a life jacket. So, I'm like, I'm
not going to go far. I'll be right back.
So, as I'm swimming, I'm looking at the
bottom. I see these really pretty fish.
So, I start following them. Following
them. I don't know where the hell they
led me, but there's spots where
you get this black weird um stuff at the
bottom. So, obvious literally freaks me
out all the time. So, I got freaked out
and I decided I want to turn back. So, I
look up and I'm like, jeez, I'm really
far out. And then
when I'm now thinking about swimming,
like I panic [clears throat] and then I
start swallowing
water
and then I'm just like I go in first
time and it feels like I'm not moving.
I'm still in the same spot. So I just
like looked at my boyfriend and I was
like, "Can you babe, please come and get
me?" Because now the way the water was
pushing me, I felt so tired. But at the
same time, I felt like I can't push to
get there. I got so scared. So I just
panicked. I like is this the day I
drown?
Yeah. No, it wasn't that deep. But like
I just got really scared. And then I
asked my boyfriend to come get me. And
then he did. And then we swim back. But
the problem is when I screamed and I
said, "Babe, come get me." Like all our
neighbors like the her and me and they
all came out to see. So like the couples
in the other villas came out and they
were like watching him drag me out from
the ocean. Yeah. And then since then I
haven't been in the water again because
we're actually supposed to go swim with
the nurse sharks. And what they said
about the nurse sharks is that yeah,
it's okay to swim with them just as long
as you don't hit them and you don't kick
them. If you hit them or kick them by
accident, then they can react and sort
of like just like bite you a little bit.
So then I was just like, m
I don't want to get bitten by a shark. I
actually saw a video of someone getting
bitten by a shark. So we've canled that.
I was like, no,
I'm not feeling that confident anymore.
So,
no. No. And I haven't really been
swimming much in the water because it's
so so hot. You you feel like you are
actually going to faint. Like you just
want to be under the air con. Um yeah,
we've been having lots of drinks, lots
of that. So, this is like our second
last evening here.
We booked a really nice restaurant which
we're going to. It's called Bo. Um, this
restaurant you can only go to once. So,
all the other restaurants you can go to
as many times as you want, but you have
to book before 5 in the evening to make
your reservation so they know you're
coming. If you don't make a booking, you
have to go to the buffet,
[clears throat] which is like the only
restaurant on the island that doesn't
take bookings. And then with Bow because
it's like an expensive like really fine
fine dining, you only get like to go
there once on your all-incclusive, but
if you know you want to pay for it
separately, you can book it again and go
again and pay for it separately. It's
just that it's like really expensive.
It's like $200 a meal. So, I get it. Um,
so we were happy with going there the
one time.
You do get $20 credit a day here that
you get to spend on anything. But the
funny thing is like the bikes you have
to pay for those. So that's like $20 a
day. We're going to we're going to
actually take one of the bikes tomorrow
and go around the whole island. If we do
get really hot,
we're just going to have to deal with it
because it's our last day.
And then so that's going to be like $16.
I don't know how much. So, they charge
you 28% tax on anything you you
purchase. So, if you pay for anything
extra, you're going to pay an additional
28%. So, like the activities, um when we
wanted to do the nurse shops, that's
$180 per person and then you still have
to pay 28% um tax and that. But, like I
said, we've canceled that because I'm a
bit scared to do that.
I'm really scared. So, yeah.
So, now just going to a really nice
restaurant tonight.
Uh, but yeah, I'm going to finish off my
makeup and catch you guys later. I just
want to get something straight. I'm
really thirsty right now. It's hot
outside. I put the fan on high blast and
I actually do my makeup outside so that
like it's set in for the humidity cuz I
feel like if you do it inside and then
you step outside, you just can't manage.
You've done your makeup for the indoors
and you haven't done it for the actual
humidity.
So yeah, check you guys later.
There we go.
Snapped.
I want to finish off with Miss Danessa.
Yummy.
This is how my makeup looks. These are
the earrings I'm wearing. I'm wearing
this bangle from from Saint Jewelry.
Yes. And then these earrings are from
Jet. Yeah. And then these rings are from
Saint Jewelry as well. Yeah. And this is
a dress I'm wearing. This is from Sheen.
In case anyone is wondering what
shooting outside takes out of me, just
go on to my Tik Tok. If you see the
video of me in this white dress,
my forehead is like sweating.
Like,
yo,
I even blow dried my edges so they could
be straight, but now everything is
reverting back. Anyway, this is the
dress we are wearing tonight. I did show
you guys in the bathroom, but I just
thought you'd get a better view. Guys,
my feet are still swollen. Hey, it's so
hot and humid that my feet are swollen
and most of my sandals don't fit. Like,
they're sore. So, if like a sandal has a
strap over it, all of a sudden the strap
is too tight. We got to look cute
because Bow is kind of like it's um what
do you call this? It's like the fine
dining restaurant out of all the Yeah,
fine dining. So guys,
I look so cute.
My boyfriend started iring this and I'm
like, "Why are you ironing that? What if
I change my mind?" And he's like, "No, I
already know you."
And he's like, "The one with the pig is
what I'm wearing tonight to go." So,
a girl must have
for fine dining
right.
[music]
>> Okay, guys. We've made it to dinner. So,
thank goodness I packed this camera
because it's pretty dark here. But it's
really cute. Like, we're sitting
outside. Um, no, this is like the
restaurant inside. They actually had two
tables set up cuz somebody I knew he
would do this mentioned it's my
birthday. So, they had flowers on this
one and flowers on the other one and I
could pick which table I liked and I
picked this one and it's really cute.
These are nice flowers. Yeah. So, thank
you for the birthday surprise. The
closest
>> my birthday was how many days ago now?
>> Nine days ago. Oh, son. July birthday.
I'm every day till the till the 30 30th.
>> Is it 31st in July? I don't even know.
It's my birthday month that time. But
anyway, guys, I'm so happy. It's our
second house. So, we got deis.
So, they just gave us tea. Um, offered
us tea. I thought it was cold, but it's
not. So,
another menu. Thank you.
Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> So, I ordered tuna tatar and then you
ordered what is yours?
>> What did you order?
salmon and
some rice krispies.
>> Yeah, it's spicy rice on top of
>> Oh, rice crispy. Oh, and what is What
the hell is this?
This is so much.
>> I'm a pigle with your dress.
>> I'm a pigle. Imagine I'm a pigle.
We've swapped drinks cuz my
boyfriend doesn't want a drink out of a
bird's butthole. So,
this is my drink now.
It's not that bad. But yeah, we're not
ordering this twiddle bird anymore.
We're on to the next drink.
Mhm. Okay, so we switched. He's now
having a spicy guava. I am having What
was mine?
Red
>> red melody. Okay. So, both have hibiscus
tea kind of vibes. So, we're going to
try these.
>> Okay. So, for mains, I'm having prawns
and then it comes with this rice and
this sauce. And then you're having
salmon,
>> right? Okay. Yeah, that's what we're
having.
Yum.
Okay, here's the dessert. I have matcha
whisperer. What do you have?
I
>> forgot what they call it, but it's got
like coconut ice cream and some
different chocolate blends.
>> Okay, let's try this.
>> Doing the things that [music] I wouldn't
like.
No, they lied to me. We living life on
the feeling right drowning [music]
trying to say I'm driving
drowning
yeah I give you my heart still want my
wallet I [music] give you my time you
want my pocket say you love me when the
light they shine but when it dark you
know they mind I buy you gold designer
[music]
why you flex for another tell me why you
like queen when say you know me you talk
say you love me [music] my money to be
me. Bring my body to be me. What do you
want girl? [music]
My body love you want my money to be me.
Bring my body to be me. [music]
What do you want girl?
Say you love me.
But your eyes
and every [music] time you might try
no me want. And baby no me go fight past
power cuz on another day [music] I go
just day my day I give you my heart you
still want my wallet [music] I give you
my time you want my pocket say you love
me when the light shine but when it dark
you know they mind I buy you golden
design outfit [music] why you flex for
another tell me why you like me when say
you know me you say you love me
[music and singing]
my be me Bring my body to be me. What do
you want, girl? [music] Not my money.
Love you want my money to be me. [music]
Bring my body me. What do you want,
girl? I [music] give you my heart. You
still want my wallet. I give you my
time.
Guys, it is so so hot outside. Like, I
just realized when you're outside, it's
so hard to like vlog. That's how hot and
uncomfortable it is. But every time I'm
in a place where there's air con, I feel
amazing. So, I'm wearing this costume
underneath. It's got matching drawers. I
don't know if you can see them through
my pants. I'm a bit bloated. We just
finished eating lunch.
We're about to go back to room. We
rented some bikes, so I want to do a bit
of like cycling. It is our last full day
here. Tomorrow we have half the day. Um,
so want to get the cycling part out of
the way. I don't know if we're going to
snorkel. Probably maybe snorkel a bit
now or either tomorrow early in the
morning. But yeah, this is like my
cutesy look. Got this off sheen. It is
see-through, but when you cover this,
you can't see nothing.
And then I've just been wearing it like
that.
Okay, it's cooled down a bit. So, going
to ride the bicycle. Babe, did you bring
your phone?
>> What?
>> You got your phone?
>> You got your phone.
>> Baby, I'm the man [music]
for you.
For you. Cuz we dance for this [music]
moonlight.
For this moonlight, for this moon.
[music]
And we go dance for this moonlight. Cuz
it's more right for you.
Cuz [music] we could dance for this
moonlight.
For these moonlights,
for this moon
and we go dance for these moonlight,
[music]
right?
[music] Yeah.
I don't know what are you playing or
waiting in line for me. [music]
telling me you're tired of the lost.
Trust me, baby. I'm the man for you.
[music]
Man [singing] for you. And we going to
party more.
[music]
And we go dance party
right [music]
[music]
there.
What?
>> Just put
[screaming]
you over there.
>> [laughter]
>> Look at that.
How cute. So cute. Says, "Have a nice
day.
[music]
>> [music]
[singing]
>> My boyfriend is out in the water in the
ocean
and I'm chilling here. Are you okay?
Please don't die. I can't save you.
If you're coming to the Mald D, just
know there's nothing to do besides
relax, swim,
um, eat, and book ridiculously expensive
activities. So, what I would recommend
is if you're coming to the Maldes, save
a lot of money to
book the activities. The activities are
minimum
$100. Actually, I forgot the other one
that I wanted to do. They had that clear
kayak and it was actually $20. And I've
been saying every day, I'll do it. I'll
do it. I'll do it. I'll do it. And now
it's our last day. And the reason why we
haven't been going to do it earlier is
because the sun has been extremely hot.
And
I didn't want to have another incident
like in the m in the in Zensba where I
get allergy to the sun again.
Already my feet are swollen really bad.
That's why I was walking in the
walking by the beach just now cuz
apparently um soaking them in salty
water for 30 minutes helps. So the ocean
is extremely salty so that should be
fine. Let me show you guys how far my
boyfriend is.
There's my There is my boyfriend over
there.
One thing about him, he loves water so
much.
I mean, he grew up by the ocean, so it
makes sense.
Look at him.
Poly.
No worries at all.
Dude is on leave. And the funny thing is
he goes back to work the day after we
arrived. Yeah, that's because we had to
move our vacation. Originally, we were
meant to arrive like 3 days before he
went back to work and then things
changed. But there he is.
Yeah.
Hey guys. So, I am ready for dinner and
somebody's late. And you know why?
Because he decided to go to the gym and
then come back 10 minutes before our
dinner reservation.
>> Health is worth.
>> Huh?
>> Health is well. health is while I was
late
and he still has all the time in
Johannesburg to get his health back in
check, you know. So anyway, this is the
outfit that I'm wearing, guys. It's
cute. It's baby blue. I love it. I think
this is like one of my favorite outfits
that I got for this vacation. And then I
went with these earrings. I went with
the updo. I feel like the updo looks
really cute. Wore my rings. Bango.
Um, I just want to spray more of this
like spritz on my skin just to smell
good even though I know it's going to
disappear by the time I walk out. That's
how humid and hot this place is. And
then for bag,
I'm just carrying a gold bag that I
carried the other day. I think you guys
have seen it.
It's this one. I'm just going to put
everything I need in here. Um, and yeah,
basically this is how I look for dinner.
What do you guys think? I'm just wearing
flops, like whatever flops I can find
that fit me because my feet are still
swollen so bad. Um, he tried to massage
them today. Didn't help. We tried that
water thing. I think they went down a
bit, but yeah, this is how I look.
Swollen feet and all. So cute. Say
Oh baby girl, you're the one for me. One
[music] for me. But now I think it's
over. I think it's over. All other girls
them they [music] one for me. One for me
know when I'm over. I think [music] it's
over. And now you don't want see me. You
know me say you see me. J you
[music and singing] can't see me. J you
can't see me. All of a sudden with no
chance for me you want baby answer me I
do baby [music] try see me I do baby try
see me yeah
it's that time of the evening again to
remove this face
um this is my last face beat in
Maldives. So, uh, my boyfriend went to
actually we're trying to check out and
then Where did I drop that stopper on
the
We're trying to just check out because
they're like, "If you want to check out,
it's best to just do it the night before
when you're checking out just to sort
out everything." Then when we got there,
we realized that he forgot um the cash
here in the room because we had some
dollars. So he preferred to pay in
dollars rather than paying with the card
cuz the conversion would have been much
higher. So he's gone to settle the bowl
and we've decided that we're going to do
a late check out because our flight is
at 9:00. So, we're actually just going
to check out of here at 6:00 p.m., which
means we have a lot more to do tomorrow
when we wake up. We have almost like a
full day. And then at 7:00 p.m., they're
taking us to the airport. Um, by the
boat, then
we will,
our flight is at 9:30.
So
yeah, we'll just arrive on time to just
check in
if there's any time to cuz the airport
is quite small. So there's probably
going to be some time to like chill at
the lounge and we would have showered
cuz it's really hot here. So if you have
that much of a like if your flight is
one of the last flights to leave, you
would rather opt for the late check out.
So, we just had to pay, I think, an
additional
$290
for a lay check out. So, we get an
additional 6 hours. So, that's what
we're going to do. And then I'm just
taking off my mirror because I don't
know if I showed you guys my feet.
They're swollen, but they're swollen in
a really bad way.
And I don't know what's going on because
it's been the last like 3 days. I've
tried like drinking lots of water. I've
tried like walking in the ocean with the
salt. I might just like spend a lot of
time dipping them in the ocean water
tomorrow to see if that helps again
because I won't be able to put on my
sneakers to go back to the airport. Like
I told you guys, like a lot of my shoes
just don't want to like
fit.
It's just badly swollen. and it's like
my ankles and when I'm walking it's
painful. So even now when we were
walking to re reception I was like so
uncomfortable and I was close to tears
with how painful and swollen my feet
are. So now I'm just removing. So my
boyfriend was like, "Please remove your
makeup." And then just like he's like,
"Please get in bed and elevate your
feet, put pillows, and then he's like,
"If I don't manage to do anything, he'll
come help me just now when he's done."
Because he took the bicycle, so he's
just riding to reception. Riding the
bicycle takes a bit longer than the
buggy, but he wanted some fresh air.
Um,
and we rented the bicycle today, so we
wanted to make use of it. So, that is
that for this evening. I can't believe
it's like our last day here. I am
honestly so shocked that this is our
last day here.
But I'm so tired. I've gotten to that
point in a trip where you're so tired.
The only problem is that like the heat
here is so draining. When we were at the
restaurant just now, while we were
eating, we both had sweat coming down
our forehead. It's so like I just
honestly don't like I've been to
Zanziba. I feel like Zanziba was better.
I've been to hot places, guys. And I
think
those places Okay, what's the hottest
I've been? Feel like both. Zanzibar was
hot. Ghana was hot. Like parts of Asia
hot. Like Thailand was really hot.
Um the occasion I went with my sister.
I've been to Dubai that hard.
The thing about Dubai is that you're
already used to the fact that you're
going to be in the mall. Like the amount
of activities I wanted to do and I
couldn't do because it was hard because
we wanted to play pickle ball and every
time we wanted to play pickle ball is
hard. And then we go sit at a restaurant
and then the only problem is that you
sit at a restaurant and you think, "Oh,
let's waste time here and then around 7
or whatever we'll go play pickle ball.
It's just that everything clashes." So
yes, it's all inclusive, but like you
can't order room service. You kind of
have to go to the restaurant. So the gap
between breakfast, lunch, and dinner is
so small. So when you think you're going
to fit things in between, you end up not
having the time. And like when the heat
drains you, you end up needing to come
like get a break. So when we be like,
"Oh, let's go for pickle ball." And then
we're like, "It's too late. We are going
to be tired. We won't have time cuz we
need to go to dinner. We just haven't
had time."
I think if you're going to come to the
Maltes, you need 2 weeks. If you're
going to do a lot of activities,
you just need time. And like when you're
trying to create content and just trying
to be on holiday, that's the problem
with being on a content creator, a
holiday is never really just your
holiday. It's one of those opportunities
for you to make content. So, you just
don't really have that much time. And
I've run out of space on this memory
card.
My god, I need to delete stuff tomorrow
so I can still carry on vlogging.
But yeah, let me stop rambling, guys.
And I want to wash my hair properly in
the morning. So, I'm going to have my
last snorkel and wash my hair properly
in I'm such a creature of habit.
Whenever I go to like [music] a resort
and I start having breakfast, I have the
same breakfast every day. This is new.
Usually, I just have the musli and some
of that and I'm and a cake and then I'm
done.
He normally gets the juices and I
normally get us like ginger shots. I
think he forgot. He got us two ginger
shots and then I brought two ginger
shots as well. So, I just got to the
table and I noticed we both got these.
So, yes, we have a lot of ginger shots
to have. Okay, guys. So, we've just
swapped rooms. We are now um at a beach
villa and this is how you enter.
So, I'm just going to show you guys
around.
Let me just increase the ISO for you. So
when you enter immediately it's the room
and then you have your mini bar and TV
on this side.
And then you go into the bathroom which
is a bit smaller than ours. Ours was
really huge
while the half beach half um ocean
villa. Then you have the mirror and a
get ready station. Here you have a
shower.
No, let me put this.
Then you have your shower outside.
Then toilet this way.
Then when you go through the room,
you've got a seating area right here.
And then you've got more seating
outside.
got the beach chairs.
You have this. And then let me just take
you through. When you just walk through
this green here,
it takes you straight
down
to the beach
here. There we go. So, yeah. She wanted
to know what the difference is between a
beach villa and the other one. We're
only here for the day. We're leaving
this evening, but we being moved because
we only booked that other room till
this morning. Like 12:00. Check out is
at 12
for anyone [music]
tonight. I'm my make the light. Oh no no
no
cinema cinema
see everything [music]
tonight and
>> one thing about day drinking and um
humidity
that's always going to need you to take
a nap. We just woke up from a nap which
now means we are checking out in like 30
minutes. I just showered,
washed my face. I got these um
I
that's from Pixie
and what I put on my skin as a base
before that which is a great base.
Amazing. This has been great for my skin
in the mild for my face is the Lancome
Geneifi Ultimate. This is the new
version. Oh my gosh, the way this just
goes into the skin. Feels so beautiful.
Um, and then I'm just going to spray
a bit of this over it.
I showed you guys this. The centella
toner. Amazing. I'm almost running out.
Actually got this from
ARC. Whatever.
C O S RX. I don't know how you pronounce
this brand.
The products always amaze balls.
Like these have been my heavy hitters on
vacation.
Um what else has been a heavy hitter?
Fortunately, I only used this today and
I cuz I completely forgot about it
because I was using my
Loiton oil which is also good. And also,
funny enough, this hotel had a really
great body wash. So that's why I didn't
have to use any of my own. Usually if
like a hotel has great body wash, I'll
use their body wash. But because this
hotel had great body wash, I use this.
Another
Oh, you always be famous, honey. is this
Fenty Skin body butter because wow the
glow every night
and then special shout out to Venus
because the way my underarms grow so
quickly. I had to be shaving these all
the time and because I'm doing laser I
can't it's not like I waxed or anything.
Had to been shaving.
It's time to pack up. I can't believe
we're going
um
sunscreen
for the body, a real one. Cuz the nice
thing about this is that it's
moisturizing. So, cuz it feels so hot, I
would just go in with straight this and
it looks like I put on lotion as well.
And it looks like I've put oil on my
body. So, it's doing
best of both worlds,
guys. And then I just packed the face
sunscreen so that I wouldn't have to
like waste. So that's that. Yeah, I am
going to dress up, pack up, and get
ready for us to
Can't believe it's time to go already.
But I'm actually tired. I was already
tired before I go. I'm tired. I'm tired
of drinking. I'm tired of just eating.
I'm tired of just swimming. I'm tired of
seeing the same people at the
restaurants. Like,
it's it's enough.
I want to go back to work. I need
something to do. And this is why a life
gave me things to do. I need something
to do. I need something else to motivate
me. We were motivated by the Maldis for
a while. We're going home figuring out
where we're going for my birthday next
year so we can work towards that. My
parents birthday is always a chilled
birthday. No, only my birthday matters.
[music]
>> You trying to me your smile.
[music] I like the way you make me work.